Um, I just came on here to tell y'all that I have, um, I just came here to tell y'all that there's
seven more black shirts available of the fascist are not your friend shirts. Uh, so I put them
back. I had, I had closed the site, but I opened it back again. I do look tired. Thank you. Life
blessings 1400. That does not seem like something you would say to somebody. Does that seem like
something you would say to somebody? You look tired. I just, do y'all think I'm not an actual
person? Do you think this is an AI chat bot? I'm an actual person sitting here talking to you. Just,
I don't know, a few weirdos. Anywho, um, yeah. Anywho, happy birthday,
Motor Man. Actually, Motor Man, I need to hit you to get some insights on some, uh, possibly on some
merch. Um, anywho, that's why I came on here. I just came on here to tell you that, well, Tyrone,
that's why I changed my pick. I literally changed my pick because that is my mood right now. So my,
my picture, my new, um, my new profile pick is really just how I feel every day.
Every day. Every day. I feel like this. Um, Jubilee looks great. What does that mean?
Um, how many potted plants do I have? Maybe like 15? Yeah, maybe like 15. Oh God. The ads are up
from my session. How are they referring to me as a black radical? Because I swear to God,
if it says one black liberal, I'm going to fight people.
Black culture is toxic. Hey, let's not, let's get on the fact that there's no fathers in the black
culture. Let's get, let's. I'm going to have a fight with Jubilee. I'm going to have a fight
with Jubilee. I'm going to have a fight with Jubilee. When Jubilee promoted Mehdi Hassan.
Then they're going to be professional. But if you don't.
Did it say Mehdi Hassan versus? It says Sank Iger versus? Okay. I'll allow it for now. Um,
for now. So anyways, yeah, there's, there's seven more shirts, black fascists are not your friend
shirts. If you want to show your love, my, uh, website, Amanda Land exports is in the chat.
That is a crepe myrtle. Oh, this is the clip that they showed this fucking jackass.
Let's get, let's talk about that. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. We all,
black culture is toxic. And let's not, let's get on the fact that there's no fathers in the black
culture. Let's get, let's get, let's talk about that. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. We all deserve
a right to exist and I shouldn't have to earn my right to exist. And that is what capitalism does.
What makes you think that you have to earn it? That's what I'm saying. I don't feel that way.
You do have to earn it. You do have to earn it. Yes, you do. That is why we are
criminalizing the floor. Well, here's what you all keep doing. You keep interrupting me when
I'm talking and you don't want to hear the point that I'm going to make. And yet you want me to
respect your point. And that's not how a debate works. If I show you respect, give me the respect
back. Ooh, I knew I was going to be surrounded by ignorance, but damn, let's go. My first claim
is it is undeniable that reparations are just and necessary. My next claim is that black on black
crime is a result of underinvestment and over policing. My next claim is systemic racism
isn't a theory. It's our lived reality backed by data and history. My final claim is black
conservatism fails to meet the needs of the working class. Greetings. I am Amanda Seals,
widely known as a comedian, an actress, a disruptor, an annoying person on the internet who always
tells the truth. And I am now an artistic intellectual who commits myself to making art that educates.
And today I am surrounded by 20 black conservatives. Black culture. It is supposed to be 20. Black
culture. It is supposed to be one black radical surrounded by 20 black conservatives. And
they, it doesn't post until Sunday. So I'm going to give them the opportunity to be correct,
but it's absolutely, none of them are white, but it's absolutely, um, I'm shocked that I was willing
to do that as well. Um, but it, but it was, it, it was absolutely, they're coming for me so hard
because, um, I'm, I'm telling truths. Um, marhaba de Yunus. Um, oh, thank you. I'm Janji, Janish.
Um, yeah. So basically like, I, I mean, I didn't, I, I did, I did the Jubilee thing, but I really feel
like, I don't know how, how they're going to edit it, but you can join the Seal Squad, my Patreon.
We're going to do a watch with me. We're going to do a watch with me on Sunday at 7 PM, uh, to be able
to, to, to do the, the, the Jubilee, uh, convert to watch Jubilee together. It's occasionally difficult
for me to wrap my head around what you do for the people every day. You are fortified with
um, with adamantium steel. Uh, yeah, I don't know if it was exciting. What brought me back to
Instagram was people kept saying, please come back to Instagram, like in person, not like bots,
like people in human, in person, like a literal lady, like literally pulled up on me at JFK airport
and was like, girl, why do I consider myself radical? Cause I'm a part of the black radical
tradition and the black radical tradition seeks to exist in no way as an extender and a perpetuator
of our oppressors. The black radical tradition connects in collective liberation. The black
radical tradition understands intellectualism, socialism, spirituality, all of these things
play a role in our actual liberation and black radicalism understands that literally just caring
for people is radical in a world that does not care for people. So now did I get to explain
all of that on there? No, no, no, I did not get to explain all of that. So, you know, what you
gonna do? Um, but yeah, I'm trying to sell out these shirts. I had seven more and it was just like,
oh, well, let me just make them, um, available. So the shirts are available. So there's, um, there's a
probably about six left. There's six shirts left cause someone just bought one. So there's six shirts
left on my, um, I mean, it's new George. It seems like you don't know what black radicalism is and that
is where your research should be extended. So, um, um, you know, I think a lot of people's idea of
radicalism is aligned to an indoctrinated and a propagandized, uh, uh, explanation of what
radicalism is, which is a suggestion that you are, uh, you know, some type of like
against order, like you don't care. Like, you know, the fact that it's radical to consider
something other than prison as an, as a possibility for, um, as a possibility for
rehabilitation is like that, that's, you know, that's the thing. Um, yeah, there were other women.
There was one, two, three, I talked to three women. Um, I didn't talk to Matthew, but I did
talk to this brother, Eugene Prair. Uh, but yeah, anyways, I have to go, but if you want
to join me for the, uh, if you want to join me for the watch with me Jubilee, make sure
that you subscribe, pay that $5, um, and subscribe to my Patreon. Bye.